MERCY JEPKOSGEI YATOR

Purchase and Supplies Management

CONTACTS

Address

Eldoret, 30100

Phone

+254727516846

E-mail

mercielee18@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mercyyator-528230223/

Website

https://mercyyator.github.io

SKILLS

- Co-ordinate the receiving and opening of tenders
- Prepare and distribute procurement and disposal opportunities including invitation of tender
- Develop good relationship with the suppliers and all user departments
- Develop and encourage cultural intelligence

ACTIVITIES

- I love reading novels
- I also love listening to music to help calm my nerves after a busy day.

I am a hardworking, dedicated and a highly dedicated person. I am passionate in what I do and well dedicated to my work. I held my attachment at Kerio Valley Development Authority which enabled me to gain experience in my field of study and learn how to develop good relationship with all user department.

EXPERIENCE

2019-01 - Attaché

2019-04 Kerio Valley Development Authority, Eldoret

Responsibilities;

- Opened tenders
- Filled request for quotation
- Delivered LSO to the respective bidder
- Delivered invoice to the finance office for payment
- Prepared Local Purchase Order (L.P.O) and Local Service
 Order (L.S.O) for various bidders and suppliers as required

EDUCATION

2018-01 - Diploma in Purchasing and Supplies Management
 2019-11 Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology

Qualification: Credit

2017-09 - Certificate in Purchasing and Supplies Management

2017-12 Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology

Qualification: Credit

2013-01 - Secondary School

2016-12 Sugoi Girls Secondary School

Qualification: D+

REFEREES

Fredrick Mutia

Lecturer, JKUAT

P.O Box 1947-30100,

Eldoret.

Otiso Ongeri

Lecturer, JKUAT

P.O Box 1947-30100,

Eldoret.

Tel no: +254728024500 Tel no: +254720360937